<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2021 08:49:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/introduction/</guid><description>Our github page is found at here.
There are five contracts included:
LsLMSR.sol - the contract to create a prediction market automated market maker using liquidity sensitive LMSR.
ABDKMath64x64.sol - library enabling fixed point arithmetic (written by ABDK Consulting)
ConditionalTokens.sol - contract to create conditional tokens (written by Gnosis)
CTHelpers.sol - helper contract for conditional tokens (written by Gnosis)
FakeDai.sol - sample ERC20 token to be used for testing</description></item><item><title>LsLMSR</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/lslmsr/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 13:26:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/lslmsr/</guid><description>Within the LsLMSR there are six functions available for use:
Constructor: necessary to initiate the prediction market
Setup: necessary to adjust the parameters on creation and to fund the market maker
Buy: utilised by traders when they wish to buy outcome tokens
Withdraw: utilised by the market creator to withdraw their liquidity after the market has resolved
Cost: returns the total cost basis of the market maker</description></item><item><title>Constructor</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/constructor/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/constructor/</guid><description>code goes here
When deploying the contract, you are required to supply two addresses:
_ct: The address pointing towards the conditional token contract.
_token: The address pointing towards the ERC-20 token that will be used as the base currency for the market maker.
The conditional tokens contract have already been deployed by the Gnosis team and can be found at the following addresses:
Mainnet: 0xC59b0e4De5F1248C1140964E0fF287B192407E0C
xDai: 0xCeAfDD6bc0bEF976fdCd1112955828E00543c0Ce</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/buy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/buy/</guid><description>code goes here
This function allows you to customise the parameters used by the market maker in employing the Ls LMSR algorithm.
This function can only be called by the contract deployer and it is necessary to be called before it is possible to trade with the market maker.
_oracle: this is the address that is required to report the outcome of the prediction market at resolution. It can either be an externally owned account or a reference to another smart contract.</description></item><item><title>Setup</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/setup/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/setup/</guid><description>code goes here
This function allows you to customise the parameters used by the market maker in employing the Ls LMSR algorithm.
This function can only be called by the contract deployer and it is necessary to be called before it is possible to trade with the market maker.
_oracle: this is the address that is required to report the outcome of the prediction market at resolution. It can either be an externally owned account or a reference to another smart contract.</description></item><item><title>Withdraw</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/withdraw/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/withdraw/</guid><description>code
This function can only be called by the user that deployed the contract and after the outcome of the prediction market has been reported. It converts all the tokens that the market maker has into collateral and then withdraws all the collateral. w</description></item><item><title>Price</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/price/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/price/</guid><description>code
This function takes the same parameters as buy().
It will tell you the price to buy that number of outcome tokens and is denominated in the base currency.
This is also returned as a fixed point integer and so will need to be converted into a human readable value by a front end.
It is worth mentioning that the price here is the price to buy all the tokens, so if you wish to buy 10Dai worth of tokens with three separate outcomes, you may expect the price here to be 3-4Dai.</description></item><item><title>Cost</title><link>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/cost/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 15:22:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/developer-guide/cost/</guid><description>function cost() public view onlyAfterInit() returns (int128) { int128 sum_total; for(uint i=0; i&amp;lt; numOutcomes; i++) { sum_total = ABDKMath.add(sum_total, ABDKMath.exp(ABDKMath.div(q[i], b))); } return ABDKMath.mul(b, ABDKMath.ln(sum_total)); } This function returns the total trade volume of the market maker. This can be viewed as the total amount of money within the market maker. Note that it does not include the initial funding liquidity. Every time there is a trade, this number increases.</description></item></channel></rss>