<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contract v0.1 on </title>
    <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contract v0.1 on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>We have provided our smart contracts in two formats:   A gist that can be readily imported into remix IDE. This consists of a single flattened solidity file which you can immediately deploy and play with. Our tutorial will utilise this, and can be followed with minimal programming knowledge.
  Full github repository. We expect users with some development experience will be able to utilise this to empower their own contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Import into Remix</title>
      <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/import-into-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/import-into-remix/</guid>
      <description>Remix is a browser ethereum IDE and will be utilised for this tutorial.
You will be greeted with this page and can click on &amp;ldquo;gist&amp;rdquo; in order to import the smart contracts.
In the message box that pops up, you can enter the URL for the gist which is found at: https://gist.github.com/abdullathedruid/f58f51e3253dde53c068e71864348274
You should be able to see the full source code at this point. Congratulations!
You can now move on to the next page to deploy the contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Contracts</title>
      <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/deploying-contracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/deploying-contracts/</guid>
      <description>In order to deploy this contract, you will first need to compile the source code. To do this, you will need to open the compiler tab and then select a compiler version from the drop down box. As you can see from the screenshot, we are using version 0.6.6.
When you click the compile button you should get a number of yellow cautions, but no warning messages. Once you have successfully compiled the contract, you can begin to deploy the contracts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interacting with contracts</title>
      <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/interacting-with-contracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/interacting-with-contracts/</guid>
      <description>You should now have deployed three contracts: The LsLMSR, FakeDai, and ConditionalTokens contracts. When we set up the LsLMSR contract, we will need to fund the contract with some initial liquidity. Therefore we will need to get some money before we can proceed with the set up!
Creating tokens to play with If you click on the deployed instance of the FakeDai contract, you should have a number of functions available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying to Testnet </title>
      <link>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/deploying-to-testnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://docs.just.win/docs/tutorial/deploying-to-testnet/</guid>
      <description>You are able to deploy the contracts to any network using remix. If you adjust the environment dropdown box, you will be able to select injected web3. This will allow you to connect with metamask and then deploy your contracts.
With gas costs being as expensive as they are now, we would recommend trying the contracts on any testnet network such as Kovan or alternatively on xDai chain (please follow the guide here to connect with metamask)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
